### Contact

08033764613 (Work) iam.ugovalentyn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/francis-valneboh-a9201216a (LinkedIn) kunyitedigital.com (Company)

### Top Skills

Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Google Ads

**Facebook Marketing** 

### Certifications

LinkedIn Marketing Solutions Fundamentals

Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner

LinkedIn Content and Creative Design

LinkedIn Marketing Strategy

#### Honors-Awards

First Class Honors in Architecture

# Francis Val-Neboh

Digital Marketing and Growth Executive || Design Architect Nigeria

## Summary

Francis Val-Neboh - copywriter, paid traffic and customer acquisition expert - has been helping businesses grow by harnessing digital marketing platforms, and strategies using trainings and live workshops since 2014.

He is the Founder, CEO at Kunyite Digital- a digital marketing and customer acquisition agency founded in 2019

His mission is to help 10,000 businesses STAND OUT and DOMINATE in their industries by leveraging the arsenal the internet provides.

## Experience

Millennium Group Growth and Marketing Director April 2022 - Present (3 months) Nigeria

Muna Real Estate Limited
Marketing Consultant, Director
August 2019 - Present (2 years 11 months)
Nigeria

Kunyite Digital Founder January 2019 - Present (3 years 6 months) Nigeria

NOVA Konzulting and Properties Ltd Project Architect February 2019 - February 2020 (1 year 1 month) Enugu, Nigeria Bentik Homes Nig. Ltd.
Marketing Director
December 2018 - April 2019 (5 months)
Enugu, Nigeria

Telios developmemt Graduate Architect April 2018 - February 2019 (11 months) Port Harcourt, Nigeria

Flexispace Architects
Mandatory Students Industrial work Experience Intern
April 2016 - September 2016 (6 months)
Enugu, Nigeria

## Education

University of Nigeria, Nsukka Bachelor of Science - BS, Architecture · (2013 - 2017)